Chuyi R. Lee

chuyirlee@gmail.com Cell: 612.226.5360

OBJECTIVE

My goal as an employee is to provide the best service possible to every customer while maintaining a clean and safe working environment for those around me. I strive to create an experience that customers can feel satisfied with while maintaining the highest standards for myself.

CAREER HISTORY

September 2020 - Present Target, Crystal MN Store Fulfillment Expert, Food and Beverage Expert

- Cooperated with multiple departments to fulfill customer orders
- Effectively managed time to meet deadlines and fulfill orders
- Maintained familiarity with changing store layout
- Specialized in stocking and moving various products across departments
- Trained and coached new employees in required duties

September 2019 - May 2020 North Hennepin Community College Office of Student Life Student Intern

- Interacted with and assisted students and staff to provide a positive, welcoming experience.
- Developed promotional materials and advertisements for events.
- Compiled and analyzed data for events
- Organized and prepared spaces for events
- Utilized specialized software to complete daily tasks

March 2018 to August 2019 St Anthony Health and Rehabilitation Center Kitchen Aide

- Familiarized myself with dietary restrictions for all patients and residents
- Assisted in preparing appropriate meals for patients and residents according to dietary restrictions and nutritional requirements
- Assisted and served patients and residents during mealtimes
- Maintained a clean environment for food preparation

SKILLS

Leadership Team Building People-oriented Detail-oriented
Time management
Microsoft Office
Basic HTML Skills
Computer and Typing Skills
Flexible
Adapts easily to new technology
Effective verbal and written
communication skills

EDUCATION

North Hennepin Community College Brooklyn Park, MN

Associates of Liberal Arts

2022